I WANT TO RESPOND TO WHAT YOU
WERE SAYING, DOUGLAS, WHICH IS
SO IMPORTANT.
I WANT TO RESPOND TO WHAT YOU
WERE SAYING, DOUGLAS, WHICH IS SO
IMPORTANT.
I THINK AS WE ALL TALK ABOUT THE
HORROR THAT WE FEEL OVER THE
SAFETY OF THESE OFFICERS, I WANT
TO ILLUSTRATE A COUPLE LEGAL
ANGLES, TOO, BECAUSE IT'S ALSO
ABOUT EQUAL PROTECTION.
AND THIS, TO ME, IS CREATING
SORT OF A GIANT LEGAL MESS THAT
RENDERS US EVEN MORE VULNERABLE.
AND UNLIKE J.B. PRITZKER, I USE
THESE OFFICERS.
I WANT TO TALK ABOUT THAT.
HE CONTINUES USING THOSE
PEJORATIVES AND THEY, AND THEY.
THEY ARE AMERICANS TASKED WITH
ENFORCING THE LAWS THAT THE
LEGISLATURE HAS PASSED.
SO IT'S NOT JUST ABOUT OFFICER
SAFETY, IT'S ABOUT EQUAL
PROTECTION.
AND THANK GOD NOTHING HAPPENED
TO A FEDERAL OFFICER OR A LOCAL
OFFICER BECAUSE I KNOW FOR A FACT
THAT IF THEY HAD INDEED BEEN
ORDERED TO STAND DOWN, THAT ALL
WOULD BE ABLE TO TALK ABOUT
THAT.
THEY WOULD BE ABLE TO TALK ABOUT
THE AID AND COME TO THE AID OF
THEIR FELLOW AMERICANS AND
THEIR FELLOW BRAVE AMERICANS IN
UNIFORM.
AND IF SOMETHING HAD HAPPENED,
THEY HAVE A MASSIVE CASE.
THIS IS DELIBERATE INDIFFERENCE.
THIS IS BREACH OF DUTY.
AND THEN WE'RE SORT OF, OH, NO,
NO, NO, WE DIDN'T ORDER THAT.
SO THEN THAT TO ME BECOMES A PR
NIGHTMARE.
IS THERE A COMPROMISED
INVESTIGATION?
HAS THIS BEEN POLITICIZED?
SO ANYTHING COMING ANYWHERE
REMOTELY OUT OF THAT
JURISDICTION, I THINK, IS
RIPE FOR A VULNERABILITY.
IT'S NOT JUST ABOUT THIS CASE.
IT'S NOT JUST ABOUT THIS, THIS
AGGRESSIVE AND VIOLENT
DEMONSTRATION.
NO, THIS IS ABOUT THE
CONSEQUENCES OF HAVING SUCH A
FRACTURED IDENTITY, NOT A
UNIFIED FRONT.
AND NOT REALIZING THE FORCE FOR
THE TREES.
THE DECISIONS AND CONSEQUENCES
GO BEYOND A SOUND BITE OR CLICK
ON YOUR INSTAGRAM.
IT ACTUALLY HAS REAL WORLD
LEGAL CONSEQUENCES.
AND BY GOD, IF THOSE
CONSEQUENCES ARE PHYSICAL, THEN
IT'S SOMETHING THAT AMERICA
CANNOT SUSTAIN.
LOOK, LAST QUICK THOUGHT FROM
YOU, DOUGLAS, ON TECHNICALLY
CREATING A NO ZONE INSIDE OF A
SOVEREIGN NATION AGAINST LAW
ENFORCEMENT.
YEAH, IT'S OUTRAGEOUS AND
IT'S BEEN GOING ON FOR YEARS
AGO.
YOU CANNOT HAVE EFFECTIVELY
MILITIA, WHICH IS WHAT THESE
GROUPS LIKE ANTIFA ARE.
THEY ARE MILITIA ON AMERICAN
STREETS.
AND EVERY TIME DEMOCRATIC
LAWMAKERS HAVE BEEN TOLD ABOUT
THIS, THEY SAY THE SAME THING.
THEY SAY THINGS LIKE EITHER IT'S
NOT HAPPENING OR WHAT WE SEE
WITH OUR OWN EYES ISN'T BEING
SEEN, ISN'T REAL.
OR THEY SAY THINGS LIKE, WELL,
ANTI-FASCIST SOUNDS GOOD.
WHO ISN'T ANTI-FASCIST?
YOU GO, THIS GROUP IS A
FASCIST GROUP.
IT'S A FASCIST GROUP.
THEY ATTACK AND HOSPITALIZE
JOURNALISTS.
THEY WILL GO OUT OF THEIR WAY
TO ATTACK FEDERAL OFFICERS,
POLICE, ICE AND OTHERS.
WE JUST SAW THE OTHER DAY WITH
THE SHOOTER IN CALIFORNIA WHO
FIRED HIS RIFLE AT ICE AGENTS.
HE KILLED TWO DETAINEEES.
IT'S GOING TO GET WORSE IF THIS
IS NOT FINALLY COUNTERED.
INDEED.
WE'LL MOVE FORWARD.
THE WOULD-BE ASSASSIN OF JUSTICE
BRETT KAVANAUGH HAS BEEN SENTENCED
TO JUST EIGHT YEARS AND ONE
MONTH BEHIND BARS.
AND THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT SAYS
THAT IS NOT ENOUGH AND NOW IS
READY TO TAKE ACTION.
WE'LL GET INTO IT.
STAY CLOSE.
HEY, EVERYONE.
I'M EMILY CAMPAÑO.
CATCH ME AND MY CO-HOSTS, HARRIS
BAULKNER AND KAYLEIGH MCINENNI
ON OUTNUMBERED EVERY WEEKDAY AT
12 P.M. EASTERN.
OR SET YOUR DVR.
ALSO, DON'T FORGET TO
SUBSCRIBE TO THE FOX NEWS YOUTUBE
PAGE FOR DAILY HIGHLIGHTS.